<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Kha Nguyen - Entrepreneur</title><link href="https://nlhkh.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://nlhkh.github.io/feeds/entrepreneur.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://nlhkh.github.io/</id><updated>2017-09-16T20:58:00+03:00</updated><entry><title>Storytelling - a Narrative Approach for Entrepreneurship - Motivation</title><link href="https://nlhkh.github.io/storytelling-a-narrative-approach-for-entrepreneurship-motivation.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-09-16T20:58:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-09-16T20:58:00+03:00</updated><author><name>Kha Nguyen</name></author><id>tag:nlhkh.github.io,2017-09-16:/storytelling-a-narrative-approach-for-entrepreneurship-motivation.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="This is me" src="https://www.gravatar.com/avatar/ab6875791f17d39ea33e09cdba38c1fa.jpg?s=512&amp;amp;r=g"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Kha. I am a software engineer. For a long time I have always loved to listen to stories from other people. Everyone has an interesting story of his or her life to tell, regardless of that person is a homeless person or a wealthy businessman/businesswoman, given …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="This is me" src="https://www.gravatar.com/avatar/ab6875791f17d39ea33e09cdba38c1fa.jpg?s=512&amp;amp;r=g"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Kha. I am a software engineer. For a long time I have always loved to listen to stories from other people. Everyone has an interesting story of his or her life to tell, regardless of that person is a homeless person or a wealthy businessman/businesswoman, given with the right storytelling approach. I noticed that when I am immersed in what the other person says, I need to use the bathroom more often than I normally would. No further explanation can be provided on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my late 20s, I had the opportunity to witness my grandfather's having passed away. I felt a void in my feeling because I did not know much about his life before I was born. My grandfather's departure made me interested in how he had lived his life when he was much younger, so I started asking my grandmother stories about how they met, and got to know each other. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hate instructions, but love stories. Storytelling is the most effective communication method in teaching, learning, and creating bond between people. The difference between normal instructions and stories is the presence of emotions in a story. For this reason, I want to improve my storytelling skill to enhance my communication skill with other people, both at work, and at home.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>